All right. Um, everybody's in the same
spots except Will. Um, good seeing
everybody. Feel like we came out of this
day with uh some good football players,
guys that are going to be able to help
us. Um, we're excited about It was uh
fun in the draft room this morning. We
had the scouts come in and and give
their players that they were passionate
about that were still left on the board.
It was good to kind of hear them speak
with some conviction uh in the morning.
and then uh some some of them during the
draft as well. So, it's always fun day
three of the draft just to be able to
get some players that we all are excited
about and uh look forward to them
contributing uh to our organization. So,
uh with that we'll open it up.
>> Kevin Ory and where do you think like
Perkins will be playing mostly
defensively?
>> Yeah, work through it. He's obviously
had the ability to play off and on the
ball. uh you know, somebody that like
Ian was mentioning, you you had good
players this roster as coaches. Uh
that's our job to find their roles based
on what they've done on tape and also
explore some things that maybe they
haven't done. Uh you know, in particular
in this case, obviously uh it's it's
some versatility along the front, but
also there's uh you know, excited about
the special teams component of that as
well.
And you talked about um wanting to add
depth and um I'm sure you were hoping to
get a fifth runner, but uh how did you
feel about the way that worked out to to
trade him to get to get a six?
>> Yeah, it felt like it worked out well.
We were able to get another player uh
with the trade. Um you know, we had some
other calls uh that were kind of going
on and then at the end of the day we
decided to trade back with Vegas and uh
uh yeah, it worked out well that we were
able to get another player.
kind of a similar question about about
Kendall Daniels. Um feels like an older
guy as far as you know his size and that
position. What's the vision for for him
at linebacker?
>> Good. Yeah, with Kendall just coming
from Oklahoma State as a former safety.
Uh to your point, yeah, he's a he's
definitely a brick guy, fits those
measurables and what he looks for and
what we look for. and um then going to
OU and playing in the venable scheme and
you see him play all over the field
stacked and the apex and sometimes even
the line deep. So he's a rare athlete,
you know, uh when you watch the tape,
the movement, the the length, the
fluidity. Uh he can do a lot of things
for you uh on defense. I know Barrett
and and Brick and obviously Kevin, the
whole coaching staff were all excited
that we were able to get him where we
did. Deion Burks had a kind of a strange
fall in this draft. He was just taken, I
guess, in the end of the seventh round.
But was there like a medical thing or or
or what what did you guys see your
evaluation of Burks?
>> Yeah. Um I don't I don't I don't know. I
don't know. I didn't even know he got
drafted. Sorry,
>> Ian. This process as a whole, this this
three days or whatever you think, how
did it go, you know, for you? Did it go
sort of like you thought? Did it all fit
together like you imagined it would?
>> Yeah, it feel like it we uh we got some
good players. We got, you know, some
good players that are going to be able
to help our football team offensively
and defensively. It was a great
experience. It felt like the the crew
upstairs. We got to give a lot of credit
to to the guys and the girls upstairs
that that helped get this thing um
organized and and it ran smooth. Uh
we've got a lot of support, a lot of
people up there put a lot of countless
hours um not just in you know the scouts
and the coaches but the whole operation.
So uh really a lot of the credit goes to
them.
>> When you're like in the later rounds is
it as simple as you know here's our top
rated player, let's get him or is it is
there a debate about let's talk about
these five guys or what what does that
look like?
>> Yeah it um I'd say a little bit of both.
Uh there are times where you know like
there's a a guy that you're targeting.
Sometimes you may want to try to trade
up for that guy. I think you've you know
have heard us talk about you know those
positional cliffs or um you know best
player available and you sometimes you
try to make an effort to go up and get
some guys. Um it doesn't work out
sometimes and then sometimes they just
fall in your lap, right? So it's case by
case and I think at the end of the draft
you're really just looking for players
that are uh the best fits that fits us.
Obviously throughout the draft, you're
looking for guys that fit you
culturally, but the best fit and uh the
best value at that point.
>> Were you guys surprised that uh that
Perkins fell as far as he is? A few
years ago, he was,
>> you know, probably graded as a first
round guy.
>> Yeah, we we're happy to get him in. Um
you know, you see you see what he's able
to do um all over the field. Early in
his career, playing off the edge and
rushing the passer and like you
mentioned, you thought this was going to
be the next one. and unfortunately, you
know, he's had he's battled some
injuries earlier in his career and he's
come back. Um, and we're excited about
the versatility that he brings and uh
excited about where we got him.
>> How do you weigh a player like him? Like
would you guys watch him like
pre-injury, after the injury, like how
how far back are you guys like watching
him? You
>> know, we've got scouts that have gone
into the schools every single year. So,
I remember some of the conversations
about um about Harold were uh from some
of the scouts that went in, they talked
about his freshman year, right? And they
talked about how he jumped off the tape
and what he looked like and uh thinking
that we were going to be able to get him
to that form with our coaching staff um
if we were to be able to draft him. So,
you do watch a little bit of before and
after and and maybe just try to see, you
know, one of the reasons why he uh you
know, maybe not what he was back then.
and maybe because of the injury, right?
Or maybe because of development or he's
playing in a different position. So, you
kind of try to weigh a lot of a lot of
those things.
>> And does it make it um easier to with a
guy like Daniels with with Perkins to
kind of bet on the development of their
traits, even if you maybe the college
production wasn't there, when you've got
a coach like Jeff who has a history of
developing these players and and kind of
making them into good pros.
>> Definitely. Definitely not. You know,
Brick does a great job. Um he's
passionate in this in this process. You
get countless texts from him which is
fun. Um but also you know coach RDE and
then you know Teimu and Nate Ali and Hu
and all those guys on our on our
defensive staff like these are really
good teachers and obviously our
offensive staff too. But these guys are
really good teachers and the proof's in
the pudding you know and and they've
shown that their ability to to develop
talent. Kevin, several of these guys
talked about having conversations with
their position coaches or their
potential position coaches.
>> How big a deal is that your evaluation
and your coaches evaluations? Those I I
assume sound like they were one-on-one
conversations.
>> Yeah, I I think throughout this process,
our position coaches are are exposed to
a lot of players uh whether it be at the
combine, sometimes the senior bowl, you
can do so many Zooms nowadays. So, so
you get on the horn with the guys that
way. So, uh, you know, our job as
coaches is to supply Ian with as much
information about the person and and
find out how the person learns, etc. Uh,
but you also develop relationships and
and I think you bring a guy in for a 30
visit, you spend all day with a player
and and you find out a lot about each
other. So, that's really while there's
an evaluation going on, there's also the
you're forming a relationship with with
uh these players. So, uh, it's pretty
cool when when you've spent so much time
with somebody and then you can finally
add them to this roster and, uh, you
feel like there's there's an already
builtin, um, relationship where it's
just from spending a lot of time with
each other. And that's something that,
as you guys know, we are in in these
meetings for a long time with our
players and are on the field with our
players. So, you you can't help but get
to know each other. And I think it's a
it's a benefit to us in this process
where we can you know again be in the
draft room and say all right here here's
what I know about the kid and you know
we're very very fortunate like Ian's
already mentioned about adding a bunch
of people to this roster that really fit
who we are.
>> So did you feel it with everybody you
brought in did you feel like you sort of
knew them? You can't get to know
everybody. I'm sure it comes up that you
there might be a guy you're like well we
didn't talk to him a ton but he's
>> Yeah. I think there's probably examples
of of of
all of it. Josh, I think there's times
when uh you bring a you just spend 15
minutes at the combine and that's that's
the only exposure because maybe you
don't have as many questions on said
player. There's other times where you
bring a guy in for a 30 visit and you go
for a private visit to their school and
uh it's it varies really by player.
>> What can you tell us about Ethan on the
just who he is and then bright kid
obviously and has the choice but what
what do you see?
>> Yeah, he's you just touched on it.
bright kid. Uh went to Rice and then
transferred to Ohio State. Um you know,
big, strong, powerful. I think this is a
guy that has upside. Um you know, Coach
Callahan, we were just talking about it
upstairs. He's sees a lot in his body
and what he's going to be able to do and
and and help him um develop. He's got
good feet um balance, but you know, I
think there's there's still room to
grow. you know, when he goes to Ohio
State, he played a little bit more
guard, did play some tackle there, so he
showed a little bit more versatility
than what he showed at Rice. So, we're
excited about uh getting a player with
some upside at tackle, but also with the
ability to swing inside to guard as
well.
>> Yeah, I know you mentioned you kind of
had to marry some things during this
process based on just when you all
joined the organization and how things
had been done here previously. Now that
we're on the other side of of draft
weekend, do you feel like that marrying
kind of like held up throughout it and
that you were able to to kind of get the
process the way that you wanted it to?
>> I hope so. Right. I hope so. Uh I think
that's that's that was the goal. um feel
like it it went really well and uh the
the relationships that we've built, you
know, over these last three months um
with the coaching staff, a lot of us
started out living out in those dorms,
so it's just natural. Um the amount of
time that you spend with one another, so
I feel like that was that's good. Um and
then just like we've talked about over
the course of these last few months with
you guys, just alignment's big with all
of us, right? and it's just to be able
to communicate and I felt like we've
done a really good job of that um
throughout this process and we'll
continue to do that. That's just a part
of our DNA and our fabric and that's who
we are.
>> How do you guys approach now this
undrafted free agent sign on process?
>> Yeah. Uh is the draft over yet?
>> Yes, it is. So, they're up there right
now. So, getting getting after it. Uh
we're looking forward to uh getting some
some players that are going to be able
to contribute for us uh moving forward.
Tom Alero reported that you guys are
signing Jack Strand, the quarterback
from Minnesota State Morehead. Is that
accurate?
>> I'm just I just got down here. We'll
see.
>> Are you someone that gets into kind of
the subtrauge and we're not going to
talk to this guy even though we really
like him because we don't want to tip
our hands or is that some the way you
have to play some of this or
>> I don't know. Um
I don't know. Is that some diffuse right
there? I don't know. I don't know
>> anything else.
>> Oh, um, Washington lineman. What kind of
just him? Uh, was it Yes. What kind of
impressed you guys about him? Just how
do you see him here in Atlanta?
>> Yeah, he's uh he's saw off, powerful,
explosive, uh really good hand strength,
uh good instincts. Uh he plays the brand
of ball that our defensive staff looks
for. He's powerful. Uh we look forward
to bringing him in and helping um him
add to the group in in the run and in
the pass game.
>> And kind of like a cool arc too, right?
Like Iowa, Western I think to Iowa,
Western Michigan, Washington.
>> Yeah. A lot of transfers. Yeah. A lot of
a lot of these guys are starting to
transfer more for various reasons. So
feel like our scouts did a really good
job of identifying him. And um a lot of
credit to Cammy Pascalone on that one.
uh she she uh really liked him in the in
the process and we were excited to be
able to get it.
>> Thanks, guys. Appreciate it. Thank you.
>> Thank you.